[Music]
we often hear people comparing their
critical illness plans by the number of
illnesses covered
but shouldn't a critical illness plan do
more
shouldn't it continually add on unknown
major critical illnesses that emerge in
the future
john's plan may cover 90 illnesses and
mary's may cover 100 illnesses and the
numbers keep growing
if comprehensive protection means we
have to keep getting new plans to keep
up with the pace wouldn't it be
stressful and costly
fwd is here to do away with all these
complexities we cover you for 141 early
to late stage critical illnesses
but more importantly we widen the safety
net by also covering you for any new
major diseases that may emerge in the
future too
how you may ask we do so by also
focusing on the consequence not only by
a set of illnesses so you'll get a 100
payout in the event any of your nine key
body systems or organs are impacted
majorly by any illnesses
or if you're admitted to the intensive
care unit for five or more consecutive
days with invasive life support
yes 100 payout with no caps
for example if you require surgical
intervention due to a heart damage from
covet 19 you can claim you're false i'm
insured
with fwd you'll not have to worry about
topping up to cover for new illnesses
and protect yourself against new unknown
critical illnesses an essential solution
we'd say
also receive a complimentary medical
second opinion from an overseas
specialist for your diagnosis and
treatment plan so that you can navigate
tough medical decisions with more
confidence
after your first claim for an early or
intermediate stage critical illness you
will still be covered for a recurring or
new late-stage critical illness after 12
months too
while offering extensive benefits our
cover is also designed to be affordable
sarah who's age 30 will be able to get a
100 000 coverage for critical illnesses
and includes a 1 million coverage for
death and total and permanent disability
from as low as 113 dollars a month
[Music]
for parents you can gift your children
these protection plans at a lower
premium the earlier their coverage
starts the lower the premium will be for
their plans
stay confident in an evolving world
place your protection needs in good
hands with fwd
reach out to our financial advisory
partners to learn more about fwd recover
first and fwd total ci rider